

 $\searrow$ 

imanwela@live.com

+33 (0) 610 72 21 88

0

4 Rue de la Mare Huguet 93110 Rosny Sous-Bois \*Willing to relocate

# **SKILLS**

MicroStrategy
Power Bi
Data Analysis, SQL
Scrum Agile Methodology
Visualization, Excel
Power Query, SPSS
ERP, CRM, Powerpoint
Data Modeling
Predictive Analytics
Microsoft Office

## **LANGUAGES**

English Native Speaker

French
C1 Proficiency

## **EXPERTISE**

Negotiations

Data Analyst/Consultant

Business Analyst

Marketing

Performance Measurement

# **INTERESTS**

Music

**Traveling** 

Reading

# Emmanuella AFRIYIE

Graduate - Business Intelligence and Analytics

Dedicated with a year analyst experience and 4 years administrative experience in a multicultural environment and theoretical and practical knowledge in Data Analytics, Marketing, Digital Innovation, Visualizations and Business Development. I am determined to achieve my goals, learn more on my job and advance in my career path.

# PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

**ALLIANZ TRADE (EULER HERMES)** 

**FRANCE** 

**JULY 2022-JANUARY 2023** 

PERFORMANCE AND CHANGE ANALYST (INTERN)

Pulling and sorting data on Policy Issuance to produce reports for analysis on KPIs set for all regions worldwide, to ensure Allianz Trade makes data driven decisions to improve their clients' experience as well as meet their expectations while generating profits. My responsibilities include but are not limited to:

- Develop dashboards, standardized reports and ad-hoc reports for the World Agency Policy Management Team.
- Support Policy Management Regional Managers on their KPIs by providing analysis, insights, and recommendations to facilitate highly-informed business decision making.
- Collaborate with other teams across the World Agency Central Team and with other Allianz Trade departments especially Accounting to ensure consistent and accurate reporting and analysis.

#### TG HEALTHCARE TECHNOLOGIES

**BRAZIL** 

SEPTEMBER 2021-FEBRUARY 2022 BUSINESS ANALYST (REMOTE)

Conducting research and analysis on the Supply market in Europe and China, in relation to the demand of healthcare technologies in the Latin America market. My responsibilities include but are not limited to:

- Market analysis, reports, data collection and data modelling.
- Analyze business structure of clients and create dashboards on their KPIs and formulate ways for them to improve.
- Lead creation and exploring business opportunities in the medical technologies field.

## **ENI E&P LIMITED**

**GHANA** 

September 2017 - September 2021

ADMINISTRATIVE ASSISTANT

Reporting directly to the Security Manager with the responsibility of managing all administrative work at all Eni Ghana locations. My responsibilities include but are not limited to:

- Supervising and Coordinating the Security activities at both Onshore and Offshore facilities.
- Attending meetings with Governmental Security Agencies and Stakeholders for developmental undertakings.
- Managing Contract with Private Security Provider at all locations.
- Financial budgeting and forecasting for the security department.

#### Achievements:

- Prepared the Scope of Work for Unarmed Security Services, which was used in tendering for a new Security Services company.
- Performed a Security Assessment for the Eni Ghana Project on Renewable Energy.

## **EDUCATION AND TRAINING**

#### **ESC CLERMONT BUSINESS SCHOOL**

2021-PRESENT

4 Bd Trudaine, 63000 Clermont-Ferrand

Master's Degree - Business Intelligence and Analytics

### KWAME NKRUMAH UNIVERSITY OF SCIENCE AND TECHNOLOGY

2013-2017

Kumasi

Bachelor of Science in Business Administration